

NGUYỄN THÀNH ĐẠT

Android Apps Developer

www: datnt.cf

Tel: +84 944 096 561 datntd759@gmail.com **Email:**

Address: Truong Tho Ward, Thu Duc City



Dedicated and performance-driven with a proactive approach and determination to successfully finish all assigned projects. Ability to build a complete android app using Java or React Native framework. Experienced with both front-end and back-end systems through projects at school as well as seft-study.

EDUCATION

University of Economics and Law (UEL), Vietnam National University of Ho Chi Minh City

Majors (Dual major): Electronic Commerce and Economics

ACHIEVEMENTS

2020 Academic encouraging scholarship 2021 Bachelor's Degree in Economics

EXPERIENCE

12/2020 - 02/2021

Intern | People's Committee of Thu Duc District

Topic: "Evaluate the efficiency of Online Public Services of People's Committee of Thu Duc District."

- Taking part in the process of handling the incoming and the outgoing documents.
- Arranging and issuing the paperwork. Tracking the workflow of the internal agencies.
- Learning about the information technology infrastructure of E-Government such as server, public service portals, websites, software.
- Receiving the response of people about the results of public services.

06/2018 - 12/2018

Part-time Employee | GBEE English Center, GBE Joint-stock **Company (Start-up)**

- Planning and implementing Marketing strategies on Facebook.
- Working with teams, organizing events such as outdoor PR campaign, grand opening, Halloween, etc.
- Telemarketing and consulting customers about the opening courses.

ACTIVITIES

07/2017 - 11/2019

The Associated Organ of Student's Association, Faculty of Economics, UEL

IT Team Leader

- Using graphic design tools for creating media products.
- Manage team and the progress of tasks.
- 07/2017 08/2018

Member | Voluntary Student Team, UEL

Help students with their problems at school.

SKILLS

- English (TOEIC): 715/990 (From 4/2021)
- Leadership
 - Leader of a volunteers' group of Green in Blue Voluntary campaign, held by The Associated Organ of Student's Association, Faculty of Economics, UEL.
 - IT Team Leader of The Associated Organ of Student's Association, Faculty of Economics, UEL.

Presentation

- Can attract audiences' attention and interact with people whenever giving a presentation.
- Can be a host on the stage, in front of people.

Teamwork

- One of the most committed members to build the plans, complete the projects and inspect the results.
- An enthusiastic member, helping other members when they are confused.

CODING









